- Tonight on
"The Bachelorette"...
- I'm ready for this date,
ready for this date.
- Hannah's journey
to find love takes off.
- Hannah!
- I am really hopeful.
- Do you wanna know
why I like about you?
- What?
- I like the way
you look at me.
[laughs]
He kind of like takes
my breath a little bit.
Like...
[inhales]
- Are you in the middle
of taking my shirt off or what?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, I was.
The dessert.
- And then...
- Whoo!
- Girl, you have your work
cut out for you.
- I know I do.
- I'm winning
this competition today.
- [screams]
- Um, Hannah, I can't believe
I'm saying this right now.
This is pretty crazy,
'cause it's so soon.
- Oh, my gosh,
Hannah, Hannah!
- I'm the type of person
when I want something,
I go after it.
- Cam's a piece of [bleep].
- What?
- What's he doing here, dude?
- Stalker boyfriend vibe.
- You stepped on our toes
and probably stepped
on her toes a little bit.
- Y'alls toes don't matter.
- What he was doing was
control freakish and weird.
You can honestly just
go [bleep] yourself, dude.
- Uh-oh.
- There's a storm
on the horizon.
- I have been asking
from every single one of you
to be real this whole time.
[sniffles]
I'm so sorry.
It's all so scary.
- It all starts right now.
[mellow guitar music]
♪
- I am Bachelorette.
[laughs]
Oh, my gosh.
Going into this situation
to find real love,
I want real conversations,
I want to understand
what makes you you,
and I don't want the [bleep].
♪ I'ma just want
that real good real ♪
♪ Give it to me,
give it to me ♪
♪ That real good real
[upbeat music]
[all cheering]
- Last night was insane,
and today is the day.
It's the beginning
of a beautiful love story,
and Hannah and I
are front and center of it.
- Treat my girlfriend nice.
[laughter]
- To treating
your girlfriend nice.
It's a new day
and it's a new opportunity
to form a deeper connection
with Hannah.
- This view is incredible.
I can definitely see myself
falling in love with Hannah,
getting married,
having a family with her.
Like, I'm already seeing this
come to life in my mind.
- What's going on?
[overlapping chatter]
Welcome.
Welcome to the mansion.
[cheers and applause]
Clearly, you guys
made a good first impression,
or an impression, on Hannah
and you're here.
What's it like night one
walking in here?
- I was nervous
coming out of the limo
because I felt like
the expectations
were already so high.
Definitely
heightened the nerves.
- And First Impression Rose?
- To have a real connection
night one
and then to see that
I was affirmed,
that she felt the same way--
whew.
Man, it just makes me
all that more confident.
- Hannah's a great woman,
and you see
how easy she makes it seem
and how great she is,
so she's really serious
about being here.
You guys ready to do this?
- Let's do it!
- Yeah!
- All right, dates start today.
- Oof.
- Whoo!
- First one right here.
You guys enjoy the dates,
and I'll see you soon.
- Thanks, Chris.
[chatter]
- Whoo!
- Okay, boys,
let's see what we got here.
Grant.
- Oh, all right.
[overlapping chatter]
- Luke S.
all: Ooh.
- Mike.
- Yeah!
[laughter]
- Jed.
- Oh.
- Jonathan.
- Oh, my God.
- John Paul Jones.
all: Ooh.
- All right. All right.
- Dylan.
- Nice.
- Luke P.
- Hey, okay.
- "I'm looking for
my Mr. Right. Hannah."
all: Ooh.
- So the date card said, "I'm
looking for my Mr. Right,"
and immediately I'm like,
"Well, she's got
the wrong group of guys
'cause I'm not in that group."
[upbeat piano music]
♪
- ♪ It's your first date
I'm so excited
to see the guys.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go. Come on.
- Let's go.
- Oh!
- Hey!
It's not easy
to get to know these guys
truly the first night
at the mansion.
They were all pretty nervous.
[robotically]
Like, "Hey, my name is...
Han-nah, nice to meet you."
And I just want to see them
loosen up.
Hey.
- Good to see you.
I'm looking for my Mr. Right,
so we'll see if
he's here today.
I thought today
it'd be really fun
if I brought y'all in
to a little part of my world.
- All right.
- Okay.
- [laughs]
So to do that,
I brought in the best
of the best for help...
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah, here we go.
- Whoo!
[all cheering]
- Wow!
- All right.
- Alaska and Alyssa Edwards
and the Queen of the Catwalk,
Miss J.
- Hmm, girl, you have your work
cut out for you.
- I know I do.
- I was like, "All right,
we'll do a little pageant walk.
It's not gonna be that bad."
And then she introduces Miss J
and the drag queens.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Dude, what did we get
ourselves into?
- Hannah just
doesn't want any guy,
she wants the right guy,
and to help her choose that,
this is the Mr. Right Pageant.
all: Oh!
- Oh.
- All right.
- We have some props
for the talent portion,
and your Speedos for your walk.
- These.
all: Oh!
[laughter]
- Yay!
- All right, there we go.
- Wow.
- Let's do this.
- Yes.
- Take your pick, Grant.
Get on in.
Come on, Luke.
- Oh, my God.
- Never worn a Speedo before,
but we'll see how it goes.
- If you need help tucking,
we're here to help.
- You ever been in
a Speedo before?
- Nope, you?
- Maybe.
Maybe.
- Have you ever performed
in front of a audience?
- Not like this.
- What is your biggest asset?
- I think just...
my character.
- Dig a little deeper.
- Go like this.
- Okay.
- Shuffle, step.
Today I'm gonna be looking
for who's gonna step up.
This is not gonna be
every guy's element,
and that's totally okay.
- Whoo, okay, okay.
- I could care less
how talented they are.
It's more about personality
and showing up.
Show up.
I'm excited to see
a little bit more of you today.
- I'm stoked.
You're gonna see
lot more of me in these, so...
- [laughs]
- So I will say,
this is my first time
ever putting on some heels.
- Oh, they fit.
- They do.
They're 15 right now, so...
- Okay, Cinderella.
- The drag queens being
fearless and embodying
who they are as a person
is just resonating with me.
- Oh, oh, oh, Sasha Fierce!
- I'm winning
this competition today.
I need to let Hannah know
that I'm Mr. Right.
- [humming "Entry
of the Gladiators"]
My final piece of advice is
if you fall on your face,
try to fall on your ass
because it's funnier.
♪ Hannah
♪ Oh, my gosh,
I love you, Hannah ♪
- ♪ Hannah
- ♪ Oh, I wanna
hold your hand-a ♪
- ♪ Hand-a
- ♪ I love you like
a "Kung Fu Panda" ♪
- ♪ Panda
- ♪ Hannah
- I can't wait
to see these dudes.
Ooh, pageant.
[cheers and applause]
[rousing music]
♪
- Hello and welcome
to the Mr. Right Pageant.
I am your host, Chris Harrison.
[cheers and applause]
Eight bachelors
will be vying tonight
for the coveted title
of Mr. Right.
[upbeat funky music]
- Man, this is crazy.
[cheers and applause]
The Mr. Right Pageant
has two categories.
I feel completely ready
for the talent,
but the runway walk?
I don't know. We'll see.
- Judging...
give it up for Alyssa,
Alaska,
and Miss J.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our Bachelorette, Hannah!
- Yeah!
I think the guys
are really excited
and also terrified
to get up there in Speedos,
and I really appreciate
that they're all going for it.
I am ready to see these guys
strut their stuff.
- Here goes nothin'.
[cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
[upbeat music]
♪
- I don't think I ever wore
a Speedo in front of a girl
I was trying to date
before ever.
But, you know, I am willing
to do anything for her.
Sorry, Mom.
- Oh!
- Ooh!
- Bring it!
- Hannah is ingenious when it
comes to, like, having fun,
and I'm right there with her.
I can definitely
show Hannah who I am
without even having
to say a word.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh!
- Sweet!
[upbeat music]
♪
all: Take it off!
Take it off!
- Okay, Daddy!
Okay!
- I'm Team Magic Mike.
I'm in his corner.
[cheers and applause]
- [screaming]
- I wanna see
everyone in a Speedo.
I mean,
throw out the Speedos.
Let's just have
a nudity contest.
- John Paul Jones.
[cheers and applause]
[bluesy music]
♪
- Yeah!
John Paul Jones is a talent
in and of himself,
but that's what I wanna see.
I want 'em to have fun,
I want 'em to be bold,
and I want them
to surprise me today.
- Next up, Jed.
- Go get 'em, cowboy!
[twangy Western music]
♪
Damn.
Yeah!
[cheers and applause]
- O...M...G!
- Save a horse
and ride a cowboy, Miss Hannah.
- Yeah!
Pa-pew!
- I'm gonna give the judges
20 seconds to calm down.
[laughter]
Hannah, we all right?
- Uh, oh, yeah, I'm good.
- All right, last up, Luke P.
[cheers and applause]
[dramatic orchestral music]
♪
- Oh...[bleep].
- Luke has the body
of a Greek god, my gosh.
The guy just looks amazing.
[cheers and applause]
- Luke P. showed off
his body in a Speedo,
which was embarrassing
for all of us.
[cheers and applause]
- Whew!
I'm sweatin'.
- All right, fellas,
head backstage.
It is time
for the talent competition.
- That was great.
[laughs]
- That was incredible.
- What about shoes?
- Luke is a tough guy
to compete with,
but in this competition,
I think that Hannah's looking
for someone who can be
himself, no matter
how awkward or strange
the circumstances may be.
Today that guy could be me.
- Yeah!
- Oh.
- [gasps]
[screams]
- Oh...
- Yeah!
[cheers and applause]
Yeah!
Yes!
Jump on down!
[all scream]
[light music]
[disjointed trumpet playing]
♪
Yes!
Play it!
[cheers and applause]
- These guys can go up here
and do whatever they want,
but I think being Mr. Right
for Hannah would just be
to be with somebody you can be,
you know, yourself with,
and this is a competition,
but it's also about having
a real connection with Hannah.
- I'd walk a mile in your shoes
to be closer to you.
all: Aw!
- For me to get to show who
I am on the very first date
makes me
really freakin' happy.
- ♪ Let me tell you a little
something about my lady ♪
[mellow guitar strumming]
[bluesy singing]
♪ The other guys want her
♪ But I think
that they are crazy ♪
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- ♪ She keeps calling me in
♪ With that smile,
with that smile ♪
♪ I think that I must try
to stay awhile, stay awhile ♪
♪ And by the end of the night
♪ She may be mine
- Whoo!
- ♪ I'll be your Mr. Right
♪ Girl, ooh
♪ I'll be your Mr. Right,
girl ♪
♪
- Oh, damn.
[laughs]
- [falsetto]
♪ I'll be your Mr. Right
♪ Girl
- Jed came out with a guitar.
It was all over.
It was just like...
can't do better than that.
♪
- ♪ Jed is Mr. Right
♪ Girl
[cheers and applause]
- Jed!
[gentle music]
- I don't really
have all that much
when it comes to
immediate stage talent.
But I did tell Hannah that
one night I'm crazy about her,
and it went a long way
just to share how I felt.
[cheers and applause]
Hannah, I know that
the Mr. Right for you
is a man that's gonna
love you fiercely.
And I've already have given you
a piece of my heart,
but I hope in the future,
I can give you all of it.
all: Aw!
- And, Hannah, I can't believe
I'm saying this right now.
This is pretty crazy,
'cause it's so soon.
all: Oh...
- [murmuring]
- But I can't hide it.
Hannah,
I'm genuinely starting
to fall in love with you.
[cheers and applause]
- Aah!
Oh, my gosh, Hannah, Hannah!
[cheers and applause]
- Dude, I mean, I'm all about
love at first sight,
but, I mean, there's so much
that you have to know
about someone to be
actually in love with them
and not, like, infatuated
or not in lust
or anything like that.
- Give it up for our bachelors
one more time.
[cheers and applause]
- I mean, yo, yo,
he said "love,"
and I wanted to knock the mic
out of his hands.
I said, "No."
- Mr. Right is
Luke P.!
[cheers and applause]
- I am Mr. Right,
and that feels really good.
Whew.
- Gorgeous.
They're beautiful together.
- [sighs]
I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't let down by that.
But there is an after-party.
There's gonna be opportunities
to talk with Hannah more,
and I'm just like excited
to see where that takes us
because there
is a rose up for grabs,
and that means more to me
than a sash.
[mellow music]
♪
- I had so much fun
with y'all today.
Did y'all have fun?
- Absolutely.
- Which one of you guys still
have your Speedo on?
Be honest.
- I didn't take mine
off until...
- Yes, yes!
[laughter, chatter]
- I was super impressed
and, um,
you all showed
how bold you all are
in your own unique way.
So to you guys for being bold
and making me feel
like a queen.
- You are.
You definitely are.
all: Cheers.
- It was a crazy day we had.
Luke P. won the competition.
He said he was, quote,
"Falling in love with her."
I could never,
ever, ever say that
after knowing someone
for such a short time.
Hearing that, I was like
kind of rolling my eyes at it.
- I want to give a cheers to
people just being real,
being honest,
don't overstep your bounds,
make sure that
this is for a real reason,
that this is love forever,
not just 15 minutes.
- Yeah.
- Cheers.
- Well said, Mike.
Well said.
[lightly tense music]
Hey, Hannah,
can I steal you for a minute?
- Yeah.
- All right.
[dramatic music]
♪
- I'm diggin' this.
- I mean, what did
you guys think, like,
about all that stuff today,
honestly?
- Do you really
fall in love with someone
within ten minutes
of knowing somebody?
- When you say those words
or that word, the love word,
no matter what
you put around it,
the individual, no matter
who it is, hears that word.
- I mean, I guess
just for me personally,
there's just no way
it can happen that fast.
- So how are you feeling?
Like, how, like...
how are you
with how I handled tonight?
- Today?
I've been thinking about it.
I was like, "Oh, my God."
Like, I've not known this man
for 48 hours."
I guess my question is, like...
How do you--how do--
it's so fast.
Like, how do you know?
And, like, it just scares me
'cause it's like a big...
- Yes.
- Deal to say, and like...
My thing is, like,
words are so important to me.
I just want to make sure,
like, everything you say
is, like, you're--
it's so sure.
- Yeah, so...I did start
developing feelings for you,
like, before I ever met you.
And the connection, seriously,
that I've had with you,
I'm not joking.
I'm being 100% serious.
I've never felt
a connection like this
in my whole entire life.
My feelings for you have been
growing, like, so fast.
I am...starting
to fall in love with you.
I am.
And I can't--I can't--
I was--I was honestly--
I was worried and scared
about telling you that tonight
'cause I didn't know
how you'd handle it,
but I can't hide it.
- Yeah?
- I can't.
- Oh, I am glad you told me.
That's all I've been asking
for is for somebody to
fight for me and be--I mean,
like, I asked for bold,
and you're bold.
[laughs]
[romantic piano music]
Luke P. told me
that he was starting
to fall in love with me,
and...I believe him.
It makes me feel excited
but, like, what the crap
is happening?
I am that girl that,
like, zooms in on a guy
and I'm like, "That's my guy."
And there's such a part of me
that wants to be like, "Him.
It's him,"
'cause he's saying everything
my heart needs him to say,
everything.
- What's up?
- Where's your crown and hat--
or your crown and sash thing?
- I set it down over there.
How you guys doing?
- The way I feel right now,
man, is that you a dog.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I like Hannah
just as much as you do,
and I don't want her emotions
to be rattled
because of something that may
or not be factual, all right?
What makes you feel that
you're starting
to fall in love with her?
[dramatic music]
- You know,
that's a phenomenal question.
- That's a real question, man.
It's--it's blasphemy to me.
It's crazy because--
- We're all kind of wondering.
- Yeah, like, you've had less
than two hours with her,
and in the history of men,
I've never heard someone say,
"I think I'm starting to fall
in love with you."
[lightly tense music]
- I know that you guys
are all probably
in the same boat with that,
but from the very beginning
of the first cocktail party,
first night,
I've been feeling like it's
almost too good to be true.
I've never experienced
anything like this in my life,
and I'm just letting you guys
know, it's in my personality.
If I want something, like,
I'm going to go and get it.
No matter what it takes,
I'm going to fight for that,
like, to the point
where I don't care
what the scenario is
or the circumstance.
Like, I'm going to go
with everything I have.
♪
I don't want to hate
on any other guys,
but I want them to know
someone who's here
for the wrong reasons
couldn't do what I did.
- How are you today?
- I am great. How are you?
- Good.
- I think she's the most
beautiful girl I've ever seen.
- [laughs]
- The way she talks.
The way she laughs.
The way she smiles.
I never thought
I'd meet a girl like her.
- You were awesome.
- Well, I appreciate it.
- Yeah, and I have fun
with you.
- Well, I have fun
with you too.
- Yeah!
- I know it's gonna be hard.
I'm already looking
down the road
of seeing her develop strong
connections with other guys.
- I think a little trip
down South
wouldn't hurt me too much.
- [laughs]
It's a good place.
- But at the same time,
this isn't worrying me at all,
because I think that's
gonna point her back to me.
- I'm kinda glad, almost,
that I'm not
on this first group date.
- Who do you think's
shining today?
- Do we know if Jed
brought the guitar with him?
- No.
- That would change things.
- That's a game changer.
[doorbell rings]
- Oh.
- Whoa.
- I had such
an amazing conversation
with her night one,
and time is of the essence,
you know?
If I don't get the one-on-one,
I'll be in a little bit
of a panic.
I don't want to fall behind.
- Ooh!
- Whoo!
- Looks like
we got a date card.
- "Tyler G., falling in love
can be messy. Hannah."
all: Ooh!
- Yeah, man.
- Should be fun.
- There's still
a group date, man.
There's still a group date.
- You were amazing.
- I had so much fun, seriously.
Like, that was such
a cool experience too,
with, like, the drags
and stuff.
Like, they're super--
I, like, really like anyone
that can just be themself...
- Mm-hmm.
- And so it was one of
the coolest experiences
I've ever had.
- I'm so glad.
- Yeah, I wouldn't trade it
for anything.
I think I probably smiled
like the entire time.
- You did really--
I was super impressed.
Everyone was
really impressed with you,
and you won everyone over.
I mean, you looked dang good
in your Speedo,
but then your talent
was...amazing.
And so just to see,
like, you still have,
like, this Southern charm
about you.
But then, like, you're open
to just all different
types of people
and to different experiences.
I thought that was, like--
as soon as you said that,
I was like,
"That's super attractive."
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
[laughs]
This was just
a really good day.
Like, it was just
a really good group of guys,
but I was really
feeling Jed all day.
He really does, like,
calm me, in a way,
and I like that about him.
Where, like, Luke P., like...
[inhales sharply]
Like, kind of takes my b--
[laughs]
That's what I always do
when I talk about him.
Like kinda like
takes my breath a little bit.
Good to see you all.
I have a Group Date Rose.
I just want
to give it to somebody
who shined
the brightest today.
Uh...
Y'all were so great today.
Every one of you just brought
something different
and just made me really
excited about this journey.
I only have one rose tonight,
unfortunately,
and I want to give
this rose to
Jed.
So, Jed.
[laughs]
[applause]
Oh, yeah.
Jed, will you accept this rose?
- Yes.
- [laughs]
- Times 11.
Man...
it's the best feeling
in the world, man.
- Thank you.
- I needed this, you know?
I didn't win, you know,
the Mr. Right Pageant,
but, uh, I think
I won the night.
- Just, again,
I wanna say thank you.
I'll see you guys soon.
Hugs.
- Oh.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Thanks.
All right.
See y'all later.
- Night.
♪
- Coming up...
- ♪ I'm here for
the right reasons ♪
♪ Ready to be a father
♪ But she's making it
kinda hard ♪
♪ When she's up
in a helicopter, uh ♪
- I'm the type of person
when I want something,
I go after it.
- What?
- What's he doing here, dude?
- No, this is my date.
- I did what I had to do.
All is fair
in love and war, so...
- Cam's messed up my time,
and I'm pissed.
- And then...
- All right, guys, good night.
- It's a shocking
Rose Ceremony you cannot miss.
[dramatic music]
It's all coming up later
on "The Bachelorette."
[gentle guitar music]
- How you feeling?
- I'm feeling good, man.
All right,
that's why we're here.
It's go time.
♪
- I am so ready to go
on my first one-on-one
as the Bachelorette today.
Tyler G. and I had
a really good conversation
the first night,
and today it's important
for me, and in every date,
that I see authenticity,
so I'm gonna be myself.
I'm just gonna have fun.
I'm ready for this date,
ready for this date.
- We had a good connection
on the first night.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey!
- Wow! Hello!
- Hi!
- How are y'all?
- Oh, wow.
- Hey, you.
- You ready for today?
- Yeah.
Can I squeeze in?
- Hannah, you look amazing.
- Thanks. What's going on?
- Wow.
- Feeling good for
our guy Ty here.
- Yeah?
- Very excited.
They're very supportive,
good group of dudes.
- Aw, that's so sweet.
They're gonna talk [bleep]
about you when you leave.
- Probably. Maybe.
[laughter]
Maybe.
- They're not. Good.
[helicopter blades whirring]
Hey, I think our ride's here.
all: Oh!
[applause]
- Tyler is a stud.
[all cheer]
Bye!
The dark hair, blue eyes.
He looks like a Tim Tebow
but hotter.
- If you need me
to take your place, I will!
[uplifting music]
♪
- It's like
a James Bond movie.
- I know. Whoo!
- I think it's finally
kicked in that this is real.
I'm jealous, man.
- The date card read, "Falling
in love can be messy,"
and I have no idea
what we're doing today,
but I'm here to find love
with Hannah.
And the fact that I have her
all to myself today--
luckiest guy in the world.
♪
- Whoo!
- Wow.
- [laughing]
Oh, my goodness!
[laughs]
- What's the topic, boys?
What's the topic?
- Hannah! Hannah!
- Hannah.
- ♪ I'm here
for the right reasons ♪
♪ Ready to be a father
♪ But she's making it
kinda hard ♪
♪ When she's up
in a helicopter, uh ♪
♪ With another dude,
I say I'd be a liar ♪
♪ If I don't
miss her too much ♪
♪ But I say,
"Forget you, Tyler" ♪
♪ But I go around the circle
♪ Nerdy like the Steve Urkel
♪ And banging
on the trash can ♪
♪ Boys, they call me
Killer Cam ♪
♪ Damn!
[cheers and applause]
- This is so sad.
[uplifting music]
- [sighs]
That was really cool.
- Yeah. I have another
surprise in store for you.
- Another surprise?
- Yeah.
Today is going to take me
back to my roots for sure.
I want a manly man who's not
afraid to get down and dirty,
so I'm excited
to get messy with Tyler.
- Wow, look at this.
- Well, today I thought
we'd get a little dirty...
- Let's do it.
- Yeah?
And have some fun.
- This is awesome.
- You ready to sling some mud?
- I'm ready to sling some mud.
- Let's do it.
[upbeat music]
♪
- Oh!
[laughs]
- Hannah's incredible.
She's awesome, she's real,
and she's fearless.
- I'm gonna go
a little bit slower.
- You're crazy!
She was going
100 miles an hour.
I could barely
keep up with her.
- [laughs]
- Thank God for the mud because
she was gonna disappear.
- Whoo!
This is my first one-on-one,
and I'm just super pumped
because there's something hot
about a man on a four-wheeler.
♪
Whoa!
I'm feeling revved up
like my engines.
I'm a dirty girl.
[laughs]
♪
I'm gonna need three showers.
I have mud in places
that mud should never be.
- Thank you so much for
allowing me to come with you.
- Absolutely.
- So when I got the one-on-one,
I mean, it was almost like
today,
just completely surreal.
Like, pinch me.
Like, is this
really happening to me?
But I kinda got
a little nervous.
- Getting the first one-on-one
is so amazing and so surreal,
like you said.
- You're telling me.
- But it also,
I think, is hard, in a way.
- There's a lot of pressure
with that.
- Yeah. For me,
I really liked Colton.
I was really excited about him
being the Bachelor,
and I was so excited
when I found out
that my name was on the card,
but then I also was like,
"Oh, my gosh,
what am I gonna do?"
I needed to be okay
with who I am.
- Yeah.
- And I wasn't ready.
I...just kind of
shut down a lot
throughout the day
and really, really struggled
with how much Hannah
did I want to show him?
So as soon as you can be open
and honest and comfortable
with me,
the better this is gonna be.
I wish I could have gone back
to myself at this moment for me
and just been like,
"Hannah, just drop the walls
and be yourself because
it's all you have to be."
- If anybody's worth it,
it's you,
so I'm gonna
try my best to be real
and develop something real.
- Good.
- Yeah.
I know it's our first date,
but this just feels right.
I mean, this is incredible.
It's really cheesy, but it's
really true at the same time.
This is--this is how
fairy tales start.
Well, I feel like
the luckiest guy in the world.
I really do.
- Good.
- This is great.
- I feel pretty lucky
today, so...
[romantic music]
♪
[dramatic music]
- Wow. This is so beautiful.
- This is gorgeous.
City right there....
- Today was so great
with Tyler G.
We had so much fun,
from the helicopter ride
to riding ATVs.
Now we're here at the beautiful
Hollywood Roosevelt.
[giggles]
- This is absolutely beautiful.
- Isn't it stunning?
It's just been a great start
to this journey,
and I'm excited to see
how it progresses.
You blew me away today.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Like, I knew it was
gonna be fun today
just because the first night
when you got out of the limo,
like, you just--I don't know.
You just impressed me a lot,
and so I knew it was gonna be
a good day.
But you just surprised me
by how natural it felt
and it was just a really good
start to this journey.
- That means the world to me,
'cause I've been
thinking about it all day.
- Mm-hmm.
- And to hear your story
about how the first half
of your one-on-one went,
you kinda came
to the same realization.
Like, you just gotta be you,
and whatever happens, happens.
That made me feel...great.
- Good.
- I'm not worrying
about being vulnerable
or, like, looking cool,
whatever that means,
'cause that's not, like--
it doesn't matter.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know?
Like, a guy's supposed
to be strong and, like,
cool and collected, but,
um, that's no way to live.
Life's too short for that,
so you gotta just reach out
to the people you care about
and be genuine.
- Mm-hmm. I think people
get that wrong,
because, like, I do not equate
what you just said
to not being strong.
I think it's really strong
that you're able--
and bold and attractive--
that you're able
to express how you feel.
That is--that's what
a relationship's about.
- That means the world to me,
'cause I feel the same way.
- Mm-hmm.
- And that kind of leads me to,
like, you know, what do you
want to do in this world?
What are you looking for
in this life?
- Yeah, I have, like,
a few, like, dreams, like,
that I would love to happen.
- I'd love to hear about those.
- [laughs] Okay.
When I was little, you know,
like most little girls,
play, like, doctor
or, like, hair salon
or you do, like, something
like play teacher.
So I definitely
have always wanted
to have a family, be a mom.
I am a strong woman,
and, like, I can do more.
- I saw that today
on the four-wheeler.
- And I wanted to have my own--
- You're definitely brave.
- Yeah, thanks.
I want to have my own career,
and whatever I have,
I want to be able to
give tenfold,
so if I can help people
but then also find my future
husband, that's amazing.
And then hopefully we can do
something incredible together.
- I mean...
what's the point of all this...
- Yeah.
- If you can't make the world
a little bit better?
[soft music]
- A helicopter landed
in my driveway today.
I mean, how can you complain?
- 'Cause I'm not
with Hannah right now.
That's how I can complain.
I really do feel like
I need some time this week.
I miss her.
I haven't got to spend
much time with her.
[knock on door]
- Game time.
- I'm hopeful that I'm on it,
and I think that's just
another opportunity
to get some much-needed
one-on-one time,
you know, to validate
and to grow our relationship.
- All right, guys.
Devin.
Matteo.
Daron.
Connor J.
Kevin.
Dustin.
Tyler C.
Joey.
Peter.
- Sweet.
- Garrett.
"Let's get our love on track.
Love, Hannah."
- Who has not been
on a date this week
or will not be
on a date this week?
Three?
- Feels fantastic.
[tense music]
- I don't know
what I did to deserve this,
but I'm lucky to be here,
I'm lucky to get
the one-on-one.
- [laughs, murmurs]
- I'm lucky to hang out
with you all day.
I just feel like the luckiest
guy in the universe right now.
- I feel really lucky...
- I really do.
- For you to be here.
I...
knew today
was gonna be great,
but...
tonight made everything...
so much better.
I just appreciate you
just being your true self,
and I hope that I continue
just to get to know
what makes Tyler Tyler.
So...Tyler.
- Hannah.
- [laughs]
Will you accept this rose?
- Does that mean I get to hang
out with you a little bit more?
- [laughs]
Yes.
- Yeah, I'll accept that one,
absolutely.
- Good.
[soft music]
- Well...
♪
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Now I'm like really
the luckiest guy in the world.
Hannah is awesome.
She's everything you could
ever want in a woman.
- Let's go check out the view.
- Let's do it.
Hannah, everybody else.
Very simple.
[uplifting music]
- Today was
the best first one-on-one
I could have ever asked for.
I just had a blast
the whole time.
Like, I felt truly free,
and that's like
the best feeling in the world.
- You make me feel good.
- Good.
Tonight has given me
even more hope
for this whole journey for me
and what could lie ahead.
[uplifting end chords]
♪
- Coming up...
- There's no rules out there,
so we're gonna make sure
that we win this game.
- To the track of death!
[all gasp]
- Well, there's your injury,
Chris.
I hope you're happy.
- And later...
- [giggles]
- Are you in the middle
of taking my shirt off or what?
- Oh, yeah, yeah, I was.
I'm really excited
about Luke P.
I mean, it's thrilling.
- What's going on?
- [laughs]
Uh...
- It's not what it looks like,
I promise.
- And then...
you won't believe what happens
after the Rose Ceremony.
- You just have to be yourself
and be real and be bold.
[dramatic music]
- When "The Bachelorette"
continues.
[wind howls]
[intriguing music]
[dogs barking]
♪
- I'm so pumped about this.
- Hey!
- Hannah!
- Hi!
Hi!
[laughs]
- We are going on a group date
today with Hannah,
and the date card said,
"Let's get our love
on the right track."
- You are lookin' good.
- Aw, thank you.
- Hannah, obviously,
looks great,
and she's so beautiful
and she knows it,
and she's rocking it.
- Well, I thought
it'd be really fun
to do something that
took us back to our childhood.
Today I'm looking forward
to just seeing
the guys in a fun setting
that's also going to challenge
them a little bit.
Y'all wanna check it out?
- Yeah!
- All right, let's go!
So let's see if these guys
can roll with the punches.
[rhythmic breaths]
[loud rock music]
- Oh, my God, no.
No, dude.
- All of us walk in
and see a roller rink
but with, like, badass girls
who are knocking everyone over.
- Oh!
- No way.
- I'm just gonna get this
out of the way now:
I don't Rollerblade.
The moment that I saw people
skating around a rink...
[thud]
[overlapping chatter]
I knew that today was gonna be
really challenging for me.
I may completely
piss my pants.
[end rock chords]
- So today we're
not just roller-skating.
We're playing derby,
and to do that,
I brought in the best
of the best,
the baddest--
L.A. Derby Dolls.
- Hi.
all: Hey!
- All right, guys,
time to gear up, hit the track.
Get ready to get hit.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
- Yeah!
- You will all need
to wear your safety gear.
You will fall.
- Oh, man.
- Someone going
to the hospital today--
I'll give it a 25% chance.
[whimsical music]
I'm nervous about today
because the last time
I went roller-skating,
I broke my arm.
[whimpers]
And I never went back,
but here I am, trying again.
- Roll out!
- So today, it's not about
who can roller-skate the best.
It's about,
like, who exudes joy
no matter if they're
awesome or they suck.
- All right, let's do this!
- There you go!
- Oh!
- Hey!
- I'm watching you, Dustin!
- Oh, God!
[Strauss' "Blue Danube Waltz"]
Come on, Connor!
- I'm the only person
who really has
any past
Rollerblading experience,
and they are looking
like Bambi.
- Oh, wipeout!
- [groans]
["Blue Danube Waltz"
continues]
- I mean, we all suck.
- In the hips!
- We're all, like,
falling all over the place.
♪
- Holy smoker-olies.
[playful music]
- Are you okay?
- I think Connor
was struggling,
but it did put him
in a position to sit down
and have some one-on-one time
with Hannah.
- This is my sweat rag too.
- Oh, thank you.
Wow. There's advantages
to being
pretty sorry at this sport.
- [laughs]
- It was a great ploy on
his end, so a round off to him.
He got that one-on-one time.
- Lookin' good, lookin' good.
I like a sweaty man.
[laughs]
[bluesy harmonica music]
♪
- I'm feeling very
disappointed right now.
I'm not on the date today.
I've been cooped up in this
house for a couple of days now,
and while I'm cooped up
in the house,
there's other guys forming
relationships with Hannah.
♪
Now I'm, you know, obviously
more motivated than ever
to go and create time
with Hannah and be bold
because, as I always say,
A-B-C: Always Be Cam.
♪
[all chanting]
Hannah! Hannah! Hannah!
- Whoo!
[cheers and applause]
- Hello, everybody, and welcome
to the Bachelorette's
Derby Dudes Derby.
I am Chris
"The Matchmaker" Harrison,
and alongside me today
to call the action,
the legend himself,
Fred "The Killer" Willard!
- The Killer! Yes.
In my roller derby days,
I was called the Madman.
You know why? For one thing,
my teammates would
tie my shoelaces together,
and that would make me mad.
And, secondly,
I used to bet on the races,
and I always thought I'd won.
I didn't understand the rules,
so I lost a bundle.
- Well, we're gonna explain
the rules to you today
as we get going.
- Please do.
- But first and foremost,
the orange team!
[cheers and applause]
The green team!
[rock music]
Fred, is it a good sign
when they fall into the track?
- That's not a good sign, no,
but so far,
there've been no injuries.
- Not yet.
- Whoo!
- Connor, already?
- Let's talk
about the rules here.
Each team has a jammer.
- The jammer, that's the one
who can score the points.
- Correct.
[indistinct yelling]
Hannah!
[cheers and applause]
- [blows whistle]
- All right, Fred, here we go.
- Go!
[air horn blares]
[whimsical music]
- There's one down.
- Immediately, there were
bodies flying everywhere,
flailing all over the place.
- [screams]
[thump, thud]
- You know, if they ever
made a movie about this,
you know who'd be great in it?
The Three Stooges.
- [laughs]
- Get up! Get up!
- I think Hannah's
looking for a guy
that's gonna take charge today,
so this is a good time
for me to shine.
[hard rock music]
- Oh!
- The jammer on the orange team
has lapped everybody, Fred.
[bell dinging]
♪
Oh--oh!
The green team taking down
the jammer on the orange team!
all: Ooh!
- Are you okay?
Are you okay?
- And
there's your injury, Chris.
I hope you're happy.
- [groans]
- Now, I'm being told
that is Dustin
on the orange team down there.
- Oh, that's not good.
- [groans]
[cheers and applause]
- He came here for love, Fred.
He's leaving
with a broken ankle.
- Yeah.
- So, Fred, right now,
the green team is down 8 to 7.
So this will decide everything.
- To the track of death!
- There's no rules out there,
so we're gonna go out there
and make sure
that we win this game.
[all chanting]
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
[air horn blares]
- Yes!
[exciting music]
all: Oh!
- Oh, the orange jammer's out,
and the green jammer
is through!
[bell dinging]
This is gonna be a runaway
for the green team, Fred.
- He knows how to skate.
♪
[air horn blares]
- Whoo!
- Huge. Huge!
- Daron scored, I don't know,
18,000 points
in the last round.
- And the champions
of this roller derby,
the green team!
[cheers and applause]
♪
- I'm a bad loser, so...
but I think it's huge
to spend time with Hannah
to show her my best side
and be bold for her.
- Head on out, guys.
- It's the battle.
You're losing the battle,
winning the war.
Winning the war
is winning the rose,
so, uh, still got time.
Still got a lot of time
to make it up.
[cheers and applause]
[mellow music]
- Wow.
- Yeah, this is like
a antique shop that also
has, like, other stuff
in every, like,
nook and cranny, you know?
- Amazing day with Hannah.
Just to hold her hand
and go skate around the rink
was unreal.
She's so special.
- It was so fun
watching y'all.
It was
mostly flailing bodies...
[laughter]
But...
everybody played hard.
- Today was awesome.
Everyone was knocking
the hell out of each other.
- Dustin, do you wanna
go with me?
- Absolutely.
- Yeah.
- Obviously, we're all gonna
have time with Hannah tonight.
Pretty jazzed.
- So how's the ankle?
- Um...
it hurts a little bit,
but it'll be okay, you know?
I honestly really appreciate
you being there, you know.
You were cheering us on,
and I think all my nerves
are, like, gone.
- Aw...
- I just got nothing
but the butterflies now.
- [laughs] That's so sweet!
- 'Cause you know I've been
so nervous, like every time--
- Why?
- I'm not like a lot of
the other guys,
like I know I'm shy and quiet.
And I do want to be bold
for you, but I just have to
find my own way.
- You have your own way.
- Absolutely.
- And I can't outdo
the other guys
from being loud or, you know,
energetic or whatnot.
- 'Cause that's not you.
- That's not me.
And I always want to be
genuine with you,
so I just...
had to wait for my time.
- Absolutely. And I...
I will say your energy
has been noticed.
And it's a subtle energy,
but it's still there.
And so this is just about
you showing me your heart..
- Yeah.
- And seeing how we connect,
how we're different,
how we're similar,
and if you do that,
then there's no regrets
in this.
- Yeah.
- We'll be good.
- For sure.
[mellow music]
♪
Today's been a great day.
I'm a shy, quiet guy,
but I can't describe
how happy I am right now.
We'll call it nine.
- Yes, I live in L.A. here,
fly for a major airline.
Kinda go like literally
all over the country.
- That's so cool
that you're flying...
these huge flights.
- There's a chance
I could have flown you.
- That's what I was
about to say!
- Yeah. There's a very,
very good chance.
- I like my wings
that you gave me
the first night.
That's really cool.
- Yeah. I was...
I was so nervous that night.
- It's hard.
It's a lotta people.
- But I remember, like,
opening that limo door
and just, like,
seeing you there was like,
"Oh, my God."
- What made you decide
to, like,
take this chance and do this?
- You know, I, um...
I've obviously focused
a lot of my career
and, like, getting
to where I was at.
So like relationships
I've had,
you know,
serious relationships,
but it's kind of been
on the back burner, I guess.
And so now I've kind of made it
to where I wanna be, and...
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm like a hopeless romantic,
so I'm just--I'm so excited
to just find, you know,
the one
and just, like,
start like an amazing life.
- Yeah.
- Hannah looks...
unreal tonight.
She looks unreal
every time we've seen her,
like...
that girl is beautiful.
All right, well,
it was great talking to you.
- It was good talking to you.
- From what I've seen so far,
Hannah is an amazing woman.
I definitely left there with,
like, a huge smile on my face.
- Tonight's a big night
for all of us, man.
Tonight's a big night.
Capitalize.
Make the most of every
opportunity you get, man.
- Yeah.
It really helps to know that
I'm gonna get time with Hannah.
- What's going on, guys?
- Hey, how'd it go?
- Oh, really good.
Man, that girl's awesome.
- You hear everyone
talk about her
and talk about how great she is
and everything,
and it really kinda
amps you up for talking to her.
- Of course, I'll jump on the
bit for any time with Hannah,
'cause I had no time.
- I'm not even worried
at this point
what we're gonna talk about,
because I just think it's
gonna be a great discussion.
[lightly edgy music]
♪
- It's a race for Hannah's
heart,
and I'm about to
basically barge in
on this group date
that I wasn't "invited" to.
♪
- I know this can be a real
nerve-racking situation,
so...
- Some guys are probably
gonna be upset,
but I can only be true to me.
I can only be Cam.
I always say, A-B-C:
Always Be Cam,
and this is a very Cam thing
to do.
Howdy, howdy, y'all.
- What's going on?
- Can I jump in?
You got a second?
- Um...
Well, okay.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay, it's fine.
- It was so good
talking to you.
- You too.
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much, Devin.
- Yeah, of course.
- Yeah.
Hey.
Hey!
- Hello. These are for you.
- Thank you!
- It's good to see you again.
- Good to see you.
[tense music]
- Did you talk to her?
- Yeah.
Uh, I had a very
brief conversation with her.
And then...
Cam showed up with
a bouquet of roses.
- What?
- What's he doing here, dude?
- Dude, that's not cool.
- No, it's not.
Interrupted...
- [Bleep].
- Kinda, uh,
had his moment during my time.
- Pffft.
- That guy is too much.
- I think it's a little
lack of respect for everyone
else, you know what I mean?
First night,
Scott messed up my time,
an opportunity with Hannah,
and now Cam's here
doing the same damn thing.
I'm pissed.
[quiet music]
- Cam showed up.
- Are you kidding me?
- Yeah, I got like
a few minutes which,
you know, again,
I think that--
- Dude, but this is not even
his date, like...
- Oh, boy.
- What is he doing?
- I don't know.
- I was very excited
to talk to her tonight,
and there's a storm
on the horizon that maybe
I might not
get to talk to her again.
It sucks.
- I know it's...
hard, you know,
not being on a date--
- I was really just excited
to come see you.
When I'm sitting here
thinking about, you know,
the inevitability of you
creating other bonds
in relationships,
I'm trying not to get
over-Hannahlytical.
To over-Hannalyze things.
- I think we're on this date
because Hannah chose us
to get to know us,
and by him coming in like that,
it not only disrespects us
but disrespects Hannah.
- That's a stalker boyfriend
vibe right there.
- For Cam coming in like this,
I'm pissed off,
and, you know, if I don't
have time with her,
Cam's gonna have a real problem
when he sees me.
- Thank you, um,
for just coming out
tonight and
making me know
that you're thinking about me.
And...
it was a good surprise.
- Yeah, well,
hope you have a great
rest of your night,
and just wanna say good night.
- Thank you.
- And I will see you tomorrow.
- Thank you so much.
- My pleasure.
Enjoy those.
- Have a good night.
Thank you.
- I left the mansion tonight
to come and just see Hannah.
I wanted to reaffirm
my intentions with her
and let her know that I know
what her expectations are.
She's looking for a man
who's going to be bold.
who is going to
break out of his comfort zone
and push the conventions.
And in this experience,
you know,
you gotta do things
to try to make a difference,
to try to differentiate,
and I did what I had to do.
- Hey, brother.
Have you seen her?
- Yeah, I just saw her.
- You know where she's at?
- Uh...she's back on the sofa.
- Oh, all right.
All good?
- Yeah. Everything's fine.
Yeah. All good with you?
- Yeah, man, yeah, I mean,
I think the guys are a little
besides themselves, you know?
- Yeah?
- 'Cause just, like,
we're all fighting
for time, you know?
- I mean, we all signed up
for this
knowing that this comes
with the territory.
Anybody could have done
what I did,
and, you know, you don't
have to ask for permission.
- Of course.
- You gotta follow
your heart, dude,
and you get that.
- Yeah. So I mean,
if you're not on a date,
group date anymore, you gonna
come out for more of 'em, or...
- She laid down
her expectations.
She doesn't want a passive man.
- Yeah.
- It's gonna get worse
as time goes on.
- I gotta go get back
to my girl, so...
- Good lookin--
I appreciate that, Tyler.
[quirky music]
And, you know, that--
that comes with the territory.
- If this night gets cut short
and some people don't get to
talk to her because of it,
it'll be pretty upsetting.
- He shouldn't have done that.
It's B.S.
- If I didn't
get my one-on-one time
and I finally got it
and Cam showed up,
I'd be like,
no, this is my date.
- Have you had your
one-on-one time?
- No.
- Competition's not heated yet,
and that's just the way
it goes.
- Can I talk to you
for a second, man?
- Yeah, sure.
- Don't really
appreciate that, dude.
- I understand.
- I do get it.
I don't appreciate it.
- I'm sorry you don't
appreciate it, man.
I really do, I'm sorry,
but did you come here
looking to find friends?
- You're not sorry, dude,
and that's okay.
I'm just letting you know
don't appreciate that.
You stepped on our toes and
probably stepped on her toes
a little bit with that,
and that's not cool, man.
- All right.
- Have to let you know that.
- No, all right.
I respect you coming at me.
♪
- The one thing
that Hannah looks for
is someone who's bold,
and I think one thing
that comes with bold
is being confident.
And what he did
shows none of that.
- So you didn't feel like
it was overstepping
like one's boundary, like--
- What are the boundaries?
Don't you wanna make
your intentions very clear?
- Without stepping on
other people's stuff, yeah.
- But here's the deal, dude,
y'all's toes don't matter.
I'm not trying to say that
in a rude way--
- No, no, they don't.
Just saying poor judgment,
I think.
Coulda been done
a different way.
Think barging in was probably
not the best idea.
But...I hope you do well.
I hope it pans out.
- Let that be a tone setter
for the rest of your time here.
If Cam's got a date
and you wanna talk to her,
go talk to her.
- Oh, [bleep] Cam.
Cam's a piece of [bleep].
In short,
Cam basically just said
we can all go [bleep] ourselves
'cause his time's
more important than ours.
I lost a lotta respect
for Cam tonight.
- Hey, guys.
- Hannah, Hannah.
- Because of Cam's
shenanigans,
I didn't get
any one-on-one time,
I didn't get a chance
to prove to her who I was
as an individual.
- Tonight we did have
a little surprise,
so we did run out of time,
so I'm so sorry.
But thank you to all of you
that I did get to talk to,
you know,
just sharing your heart
and allowing me to share mine,
so...
Um...
I wanna give this rose
to...
Dustin because
I asked for somebody
when we fall--
'cause we're all gonna fall--
to get back up,
and you did that, literally.
And I'm just really
impressed by you today.
So, Dustin,
will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
[soft music]
♪
- Well, I hope you all
had a really good time tonight.
I sure did.
But I'm also really tired.
[laughter]
- Yeah.
- And we have a big night
tomorrow night,
the cocktail party,
so rest up,
and I'll see y'all soon.
- Yes, ma'am.
- You got it.
- I would have loved
to gone have out there
and just grabbed Cam
by the jacket
and just pushed him
back into the van
and told him to [bleep] off
and get out of there.
But I'm not that type of
aggressor.
- Good night, Kevin.
- It's just gonna make me
really sad if I get sent home
because my name starts to
dissolve from her memory.
- Good night, y'all.
- Good night, Hannah.
- See ya, Hannah.
[soft music]
- Coming up...
- I'm really excited
about Luke P.
- The cocktail party
gets crazy.
- Are you in the middle
taking my shirt off?
- Yeah, yeah, I was.
He's so hot,
I mean, it's thrilling.
- And then,
after the Rose Ceremony...
- All right, guys, good night.
- Things really heat up.
- You just have to be bold.
[soft music]
♪
- I think it's gonna be weird
to have people go home
just because, you know,
it's been a pretty
insane week, right?
- Yeah.
[door opens]
- Ooh.
- Hey, guys.
- Wow.
Love the dress.
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
- This is for you.
- Thank you.
Um...
I'm sorry.
[voice breaks]
I'm so sorry.
[tearfully]
Um, so...
[sniffles]
I've been asking
from every single one of you
to be real this whole time
[sniffles]
with me, so I...
I wanna be real with you
and, um,
this week has been...
[sniffles] so amazing.
I couldn't have asked for
a better group of guys
to make me feel deserving
and...
fought for, and, um,
[sniffles]
just really special.
But...
[sniffling]
- Get some Kleenex?
- Here.
- Um...
Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm just being completely
like--
This is me right now.
- It's okay.
- Um...and it's--
I think about you guys.
I just get overwhelmed
by emotions of just like
how lucky I am.
And it's also scary,
and it's hard to make
decisions...
when I don't know all you
that well
as I want to,
and I know that
love can be messy.
Love can...
be something
you just have to roll with.
[laughs]
But I wanna find
a Mr. Right in all this.
So cheers to
a really amazing night
ahead to just
have real moments together.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Somebody give her a hug.
- Wanna come with me
a little bit?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Come on.
[soft music]
- I'm so sorry.
- It's all good.
♪
I know it's been--
been a long week, but--
- It's been a long week.
It's been a great week.
- Yeah.
I'm just really thankful.
- I think all week
I've just been like...
feel really blessed
and, um...
so it's tough in a way too.
- Yeah.
Definitely.
Well, I really want to
be there for you,
and I know I can be.
- Thank you.
- I think from experiences
in my life
that I wanna share to you
at some point...
- Yeah.
- And open up to you about,
but, you know,
time is so precious.
You need to make the most
of it when you have it.
So even not being on a date,
I wanna make the most of that
with you, you know,
cherish our time together.
- I thought about you a lot
this week.
But I feel really good
with where we're at,
so...
- That means a lot to me.
- Yeah. I...
think there's definitely
a connect--
I know there's a connection.
- Yeah.
- And I...
I enjoy being with you.
- Yeah?
[soft music]
♪
You're so amazing.
- You're so sweet.
Hope I didn't make you
feel like a bummer.
- No.
- Well, I got you with me.
- Yeah. I was really looking
forward to talking to you.
- I feel very lucky,
and I have, like,
more than I could ever want.
- Hey, guys.
- Oh, hey!
- Hey, man.
- Do you mind if I steal her
for a little bit?
- Oh, no, for sure.
- But this is about me
deciding
what type of person
I wanna spend
the rest of my life with
and for them to know
what they're getting.
And that's a strong,
emotional,
real, bold woman.
Who's not scared of...
Laying it all out there.
- I know we both
had rough weeks,
obviously going on dates
with lots of guys.
You need a release
every once in a while.
- Yeah.
- So, if you want,
I mean,
it's a beautiful night.
Do you wanna just scream
at the top of your lungs
and kind of get that
pent-up tension out?
- Let's do it.
- Really? Okay.
- Yeah.
- One...
two...three.
- Aah!
- [exhales]
- It's a little freeing,
isn't it?
- Why do I like to scream?
- That was amazing.
- That was awesome.
- Thank you so much.
- Wait, so where did you
learn this?
- Um, so...
[low chatter]
- Yeah! I don't know anything.
So are you still
in the military?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay. Okay.
"Yes, ma'am."
I like that.
It's the best.
Um...
- Hey, guys.
I actually got
something planned
for all three of us.
So you wanna come down here?
- Thank you.
- It's right this way.
- Okay.
- Little chilly,
so we'll make this quick, guys.
- Okay.
- So let's get comfy here.
Hannah in the middle,
obviously.
When I came here,
I promised myself one thing.
Very simple: A-B-C:
Always Be Cam.
And I'm the type of guy
that when I want something,
I go all in.
When we had our first
one-on-one here,
we kinda had a little
fun-loving, joking conversation
about how picky
of an eater I was.
And, um, that being said,
I got us some nuggets here.
And, um, Hannah...
- Yes?
- Will you accept...
this honey mustard?
- [gasps] Yes!
Yes!
- Yeah.
Cheers. To a bright future.
- Cheers!
- What the heck?
It's kind of insane, honestly.
- Thank you, Sinclair.
Appreciate you, buddy.
- Yes, it is a competition
at the end of the day,
but what he was doing was
control freakish and weird.
- What's up, buddy?
- [bleep] Cam.
Cam's a piece of [bleep].
- Did you talk to her?
- Yeah it was [bleep] splendid.
- Oh, right.
Now I need to hear about this.
- It was splendid
until Cam introduced himself
again, and then, uh...
now he's having a chicken
nugget ceremony with her.
- What's that?
- Ceremony?
- I don't--What would you
call it?
I guess it was like a...
I mean, you obviously did it.
You can explain.
- Yeah, yeah,
so I wanted to keep it
as light-hearted as possible
and even asked my boy Kevin
to join us
in a rose-shaped heart.
- Definitely didn't
expect this at all.
But as I learned,
and as Cam has taught us,
anything can happen.
- Dude went on a mission right?
- Who's that?
- I just wanted to address
really quick--
I think you're just coming
at a really weird angle
with trying to impose
your will.
I think what you did with me
tonight was honestly ridiculous
as well, and with the whole
chicken nuggets thing,
I think you can honestly
just go [bleep] yourself, dude.
- Whoa, hey, hey.
[dramatic music]
- All right.
♪
- It's good to see
that smile again.
- I know.
- Wow.
You are absolutely,
once again,
captivating
and killing that red dress.
- Thank you.
- You enjoying
this frigid night?
- No, I'm so cold.
- Come here, get in here.
I am so excited to see Hannah.
I mean, she's captivating.
She steals you
right in the moment
and everything is just her.
It's a special feeling
to be with her.
I wanted to come see you.
- Thank you.
- I wanted to tell you,
you know, I, uh...
that night I saw you,
when I first
came out of the limo...
- Mm-hmm?
- It, uh, gave me this feeling
that I got
when I was playing football
when you come outta
the tunnel.
I'm sure when
you're in Tuscaloosa,
you're in Alabama--
- I got to go through
the tunnel.
- You got to go through
the tunnel? So you get
where I'm comin' from.
- Yes. I'm picturing it
right now.
- And you get these amazing
butterflies,
like the best feeling
in the world.
You know what I mean?
And seeing you was like
the first thing
that ever gave me
that feeling again.
And I still get it
every time I see you.
It's crazy.
And it just means that
you're something
super special to me.
- I appreciate you being
vulnerable and honest
with, like, where you're at
in your feelings, and that's--
- I'm an open book.
So you're gonna get everything.
- Same.
- And I got no problem
sharing it with you.
- Do you wanna know
what I like about you?
- What?
- Well, I like the way
you look at me.
- Well, I can keep doing that
for you, all right?
- I'm like...ohh.
- That's pretty easy to do.
- You just make me feel like
very, like--
When you're there,
you're...
- I'm locked in.
- You're locked in.
- And I noticed it,
and I like it.
A lot.
- Well, it's hard to
keep my eyes off you. so...
- Thank you.
- That's all right.
[soft music]
♪
- You gotta respect
how real she is.
- Yeah.
- She's like really
invested in this,
you know what I mean?
She really wants to connect
with someone
on a very deep level.
- That's true, man.
- Jed, what's your approach
tonight,
since you already got a rose?
- I obviously do wanna
talk to her.
I will talk to her.
But I just kinda wanted you
guys to get your shot.
I already have a rose
going into this.
I feel super confident.
I just--you know,
I'm looking for, hopefully,
just five minutes
with Hannah tonight
just to let her know that
I've been thinking about her
because I'm really excited
for our next interaction.
- Well, I wanted you
just to relax,
and I know that this is
stressful.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I wanted you
just to let go
and unwind a little bit.
And this is--This right here...
- Mm-hmm.
- Is a sneak peek
of what can come down the road.
[both laugh]
- Oh, that's it.
- Hey, um, you'll learn
I'm really good with my hands.
- Oh--
- And...
If you ever want a massage--
Here. I'll zip you up.
Sorry.
- Zip me up
and come right back here.
- Yes.
[laughs]
- Okay, my turn.
- Yeah?
- You can take your shirt
off and lay down.
I'm really excited
about Luke P.
Because I just like get excited
when I'm gonna see him.
I mean, it's thrilling.
[bluesy music]
♪
He's so hot,
it's easy to get caught up
in what this is.
[giggling]
All right.
- Are you in the middle of
taking my shirt off, or--
- Yeah, yeah, I was.
I was just gonna rub oil
on your body and--
[laughs]
It's like, can we just
skip the main course
and go to the dessert?
Luke P. is the dessert.
♪
- What's going on?
- Uh...massages, actually.
- Oh.
- I know this is not what you
wanted to see right now.
- Yeah, man.
- It's not what it looks like.
I promise.
- That's, uh, that's not...
super, uh,
not super appealing, man.
Um...
- Hold on one second.
- Yeah, you're good.
- Just a few minutes, please.
- Yeah.
- I don't know
what I need to do.
[bleep, bleep, bleep,
bleep, bleep]
[bleep] me! [bleep] me!
- Sorry.
- Sorry. I don't usually
say the F-word a lot,
but...[bleep]!
Okay.
- That's my fault.
Honestly.
Well, let's go in
and talk with him.
- I don't know what to do.
Uh...
I don't know--I don't know
what I can do.
I don't know what to do.
[soft music]
♪
- [bleep].
Hey.
- Hi.
How are you?
- I'm okay.
That was...
that was awkward.
- [laughing]
- I'm not gonna lie.
- It's okay.
It's to be expected.
You know what's really weird
that I've noticed,
that there's, like,
there's a lot of dudes
in here that are after you.
Isn't that weird?
[both chuckle]
It's fine.
- [groans] Ohh!
I did not--
It's just awkward.
- This is harder for you
than it is for me, I promise.
- Yeah, but I do enjoy
my time with you,
and it--First of all,
it looks way more than it was.
And so I'm like--
Ah! No.
That's not--I'm--
It's a massage.
Funny.
- That's okay.
It is kinda funny
if you think about it.
I didn't know
if I was like,
um...should I give them
a second
or should I walk out,
you know?
It's like a battle of like--
- I think it more was like
this is just freakin' weird.
- I should have walked back
in the room with my pants off.
- [laughing] Yes!
Like, "Hey, uh, can I
score for a second?"
- Yeah.
"If we're massaging..."
- Jed, yes!
I would have...died.
- I would have done it--
- And I would have said,
"All right, gonna miss you.
Bye, Luke."
I'm glad that you...
don't make me feel--
Act like--
we can laugh about it.
- Yeah.
- I was a little rattled
at first,
but with everything the way
it kinda went down,
I had to kind of laugh it off,
and Hannah, like,
she appreciated that a lot.
You could tell it, like,
bothered her
and maybe embarrassed her
a little bit,
but, you know,
if you go around being
jealous or worried--
it's never paid off
one time in my life.
Ever.
- Thank you so much,
all of you, seriously.
I...came in emotional,
but I think it's because
this is already
been so great because
of every single one of you
making...me feel
so expectant of what's ahead.
But I have some decisions
I need to be made,
and I'll see you
at the Rose Ceremony.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Going into tonight, the
stakes are very, very high.
I'm looking around the room,
and I see 22 solid candidates
to move forward,
but that's not gonna happen.
- Honestly, I don't know
who's going home tonight.
I have no doubt there will be
more curveballs coming through,
and we'll see
who gets the roses.
[soft music]
♪
- It's still so weird
standing up here.
[light laughter]
Um...
This is hard already.
I didn't expect it.
But I already have got
to know all of you so much
and respect the hell
out of every single one of you
standing up here today
and exposing your heart
to me, so
know that I'm just
trying to...
make the best decisions
for myself.
[suspenseful music]
♪
Tyler C.
Tyler C., will you
accept this rose?
- Always, Hannah.
♪
- Garrett?
Garrett,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes, ma'am.
- I feel like I have
a pretty good idea
of what Hannah's looking for,
and I can see Cam
going home tonight.
- Devin.
Devin, will you
accept this rose?
- Yes.
- Just knowing Hannah,
I mean, she's nonstop talk
about being bold,
but Cam's the wrong
kind of bold.
- Connor S.
- I totally understand
his mentality.
- Will you accept this rose?
- Yes.
- But do I think
he's dug his own grave?
Maybe.
- Luke P.
Luke, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
- Dylan?
- Right now,
I feel a little shaky.
- Will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
- Ultimately,
we're all here for Hannah
and what's best for her.
She knows what she wants,
and anything can happen, man.
- Luke S.
- There's, you know, only
so many roses to be handed out
and it's not lost on me
that I'm on the chopping block,
you know?
- Mike.
- 'Scuse me.
- Mike, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely.
- My mind is thinking about
so many different things
right now.
- Peter.
- There's tons of things
that I wish I could have done
better or differently
since obviously you only get
one chance at love,
and I feel like
this might be it.
- Kevin.
Kevin, will you accept
this rose?
- Every single time.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Jonathan.
Will you accept this rose?
- With honor.
[suspenseful music]
- Joey.
Will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
Thank you.
- I'm the type of guy that,
when I want something,
I go all in.
- Matteo.
- I don't wanna be passive,
because Hannah straight up
said that's not
what she wants.
She wants a bold man.
- John Paul Jones.
Will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- There are no rules.
There is no handbook
on how to win Hannah over.
- Grant.
- All is fair
in love and war,
so I'm gonna continue
to be Cam,
and I'm confident
that I'll get that rose.
[dramatic chords]
- Hannah, gentlemen,
this is the final rose
tonight.
When you're ready.
[intense music]
♪
Cam.
Cam, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Gentlemen, I'm sorry.
You did not receive a rose.
Take a moment.
Say your good-byes.
[low chatter]
- Hannah,
thank you.
- Thank you.
- Follow your heart.
- See you later.
- You take care.
- Take care. Absolutely.
- Tonight was a total
roller coaster of emotions.
Highs and lows.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you, Daron.
But that's life.
- Mm.
- It is hard to tell somebody
that, like, it's just not
meant to be.
- Okay.
- But I just have to make
decisions
that I feel are best.
I'm really excited about
the group of men
that I still have here,
and I am continuing
to look for
men that make bold moves.
- To my future best friend,
Ms. Hannah Ayala.
- Ayala?
- That's my last name.
- Oh. I didn't know--
- We're not gonna cheer
his name.
[all booing, groaning]
- Gotta be bold, fellas.
Gotta be bold.
- All right.
- Sweet dreams.
- Good night!
[soft music]
- All right, guys, good night.
♪
- Did she not affirm what I was
telling you guys all along?
You just have to be yourself
and be real and be bold.
- I'm looking for a man
that--he is just here for me,
but in different ways
I guess I want it.
Like, even with Tyler G.
I was like--
[footsteps]
Hey.
- Hello.
- What are you doing?
- I'm coming to talk to you.
[both laughing]
- Hey.
- How are you doing?
Ohh...
- [murmurs]
- [laughs] Do you?
Nice and comfy?
- Mm-hmm.
- How're you doing?
- I wanna go talk to you
more.
- Okay, perfect.
- Right here?
Are you talking right here?
We have to talk right here?
- We can talk
wherever you want.
- Okay.
Um...
this is--Pull up the...
or sit right here.
- Why don't you just
sit in my lap?
- Yeah.
- How's that sound?
This seriously just already
means the world to me.
- What means the world
to you?
- Just wanted you to spend
more time with me
and talk to me.
- Yeah, you told me
that you're starting
to fall in love with me.
- Yes.
- That is like a really...
like big words to say,
and I don't want--
And I just, like--
- Okay, so...
- It's not like
a competitive thing.
I'm just being honest...
- Yeah.
- 'Cause, like, I--
- Can I just--
- Yeah, just talk.
- So...
I feel like everything
in time stopped,
like when I was looking
you in the eyes
for the first time, and...
honestly, everything's been
just like magical,
I feel like, meeting you.
- Yeah.
- I just want you to know
seriously, I am--
[soft music]
♪
[music swells]
- Next week,
on "The Bachelorette"...
- Find a man that's gonna
be there with me
through all the pain,
and I mean all the pain.
[electric sizzling]
- Aah!
[laughter]
- All the guys are making me
feel so good.
- I'm so smiley around you.
- Wanna feel it?
Behave, girl, behave.
- Yeah, yeah.
That is what Mama
used to say.
- Quite honestly,
you give me hope.
- I can't stop thinking
about you, and I love that.
That could be my wife
right there.
♪
- You guys have
really good energy.
- She's kissing other guys,
and it's not an easy pill
to swallow.
I just need to get something
off my chest
with you real quick.
- Later, okay?
I need him to slow his roll.
- Luke's self-imploding.
- There's something I need
to discuss with Hannah.
- Cam told us that he was
gonna tell you a sad story
to kind of get the pity rose.
- This just feels really
schemey and slimy.
- Whoa!
- What just happened?
- This is my worst nightmare.
- It's all coming up
next week
on "The Bachelorette."
- I have like a little
surprise for you.
- Oh, yeah!
- I told you about
how I moved around a lot
and I like to be adventurous,
and that's kinda one thing
that I'm attracted to in you.
- Yeah.
- And so when I saw you,
you were definitely being
very adventurous in Thailand,
and you ate a bug.
But unfortunately, Colton...
- Didn't eat the bug.
- No. And I thought
that was messed up.
- What was that?
It was messed up!
- Yeah. So...
- Oh, fudge.
Do I eat a bug?
- No, no.
- [gasps]
- You don't have to eat it.
We have a couple
different kinds.
And you can pick
which one I eat.
- I want you to eat
all of 'em.
- All of them.
- Yes.
Can you do it?
- So like in one handful?
- Yeah.
- Okay, I feel like--
- Mix it up.
I feel like if you do it
all at one time...
- Yeah, I don't wanna do
one at a time.
You're not taking this
easy on me, huh?
- No.
- All right, well,
here we go.
- [crunching]
- Crush it, crush it!
Crush it, crush it!
[playful music]
Oh, there's a little--
I'm just kidding!
[both laughing]
I see a little wing.